Finding Aid for Theodore J. St. Antoine Papers 1966-1993
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Public Service/Committee Work
  - Michigan Governor's (Blanchard) Special Counselor on Workers' Compensation
    - Volume II
      - Interviews (Includes notes and correspondence) 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Joseph, Lawrence--Industrial Diseases Report 1984 (Box 11)
      - Larson, Arthur--Exclusivity and Third-Party Issues Report 1984 (Box 11)
      - Minnesota/Wisconsin Trip August 1984 (Box 11)
      - National Symposium on Worker's Compensation--University of Maine
        - July 1984 (Box 11)
        - July 1985 (Box 11)
      - News Clippings 1984-1985 (Box 11)
      - Ohio Trip September 1984 (Box 11)
    - Volume III
      - Background 1984-1986, 14 folders; 2 volumes (Box 11)
      - Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 12)
      - Mailing List 1985 (Box 12)
      - Sources for Final Report 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Michigan State Bar
    - Committee on Judicial Qualifications 1974-1978 (Box 12)
    - Scope and Correlation Committee 1973-1978 (Box 12)
  - Minority Academic Advancement Program (Tutor) 1976-1982, undated (Box 12)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators
    - Annual Meetings
      - 1968 (Box 12)
        (Speaker--"The Role of Law in Arbitration: Comments")
      - 1977 (Box 12)
        (Speaker--"Judicial Review of Labor Arbitration Awards: A Second Look at Enterprise Wheel and Its Progeny")
      - 1981 (Box 12)
        (Speaker--"Protection Against Unjust Discipline: An Idea Whose Time Has Long Since Come")
      - 1982 (Program Committee Chairman), 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Committee on Alternative Dispute Resolution 1981-1993 (Box 12)
    - Committee on the Development of New Arbitrators 1983-1988 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence 1982-1993, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Membership 1978 (Box 12)
  - National Resource Center for Consumers of Legal Services
    (President, 1976-1978/Board of Directors)
    - Correspondence 1978-1985 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee Meetings
      - June 4, 1976 (Box 12)
      - November 23, 1976 (Box 12)
      - May 19, 1977 (Box 12)
      - August 8, 1977 (Box 12)
      - August 30, 1977 (Box 12)
      - October 13, 1977 (Box 12)
      - November 1, 1977 (Box 12)
      - February 1, 1978 (Box 12)
      - August 10, 1978 (Box 12)
      - November 10, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Research Club (President) 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - UAW-GM Legal Services Plan (Chair)
    - Administrative Committee Meetings
      - June 21, 1979, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - September 21, 1979 (Box 13)
      - October 19, 1979 (Box 13)
      - December 10, 1979 (Box 13)
      - January 21, 1980 (Box 13)
      - April 22, 1980 (Box 13)
      - July 8, 1980 (Box 13)
      - September 8, 1980 (Box 13)
      - November 24, 1980 (Box 13)
      - January 26, 1981 (Box 13)
      - April 20, 1981 (Box 13)
      - July 20, 1981 (Box 13)
      - October 13, 1981 (Box 13)
      - January 5, 1982 (Box 13)
      - April 12, 1982 (Box 13)
      - July 12, 1982 (Box 13)
      - November 15, 1982 (Box 13)
      - June 20, 1983 (Box 13)
      - July 25, 1983 (Box 13)
      - October 10, 1983 (Box 13)
      - November 29, 1983 (Box 13)
      - February 6, 1984, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - June 4, 1984, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - November 26, 1984 (Box 14)
      - December 17, 1984 (Box 14)
      - April 24, 1985 (Box 14)
      - July 11, 1985, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - October 11, 1985 (Box 14)
      - December 9, 1985 (Box 14)
      - March 20, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Agreement with AFSCME 1985 (Box 14)
    - Audited Financial Statements 1978-1984 (Box 14)
    - Collective Bargaining Committee 1980 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous 1980-1985 (Box 14)
    - Proposal to Provide Professional Services (by Cooper & Lybrand and Barrow, Aldridge & Co.) 1983 (Box 14)
  - University of Minnesota Law School Inspection 1972, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Washtenaw County Circuit Court Steering Committee (Chair) 1978 (Box 14)